

### **PROFILE**

A passion and well-trained front-end developer. Throughout various project, i have acquired neccesary front-end skill-sets. Besides that, i have developed ability in time management and team-work during previous working experiences. Therefore, I am reliability adaptable and handling well challenges as well as working under pressure. Learning new technologies and sharpening IT skills are my main future targets.

#### CONTACT

PHONE: +358 468 870 694

EMAIL: tuanbinh.35@gmail.com

LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/tuan-binh-dang-54298910b

GITHUB:

https://github.com/dangtuanbinh

PERSONAL SITE:

personal-cv-2343b.web.app

#### **SKILLS**

- ✓ HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT
- ✓ Bootstrap, SCSS, ES6
- ✓ React.js
- ✓ Redux, Context API
- ✓ API, Firebase services
- ✓ GITHUB

#### **LANGUAGE**

# DANG TUAN BINH

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Mellow

- Number of team member: 1
- Position: Front-end developer
- **❖ Duration:** 3.5 months
- Project idea: a social network, target to cat's owners.
- Project descriptions:
  - o Techniques: HTML5, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT
  - o Library/ Framework: React.js
  - o Additional: Context API, Firebase database and services, React-bootstrap, Material UI.
  - o Project link: mellow-83a7f.web.app

## Cyberpunk Academy

- Number of team member: 3
- Position: Front-end developer and team leader.
- **Duration:** 5 months
- Project idea: an online teaching platform. Inspired by Udemy website.
- Project descriptions:
  - Techniques: HTML5, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT.
  - Library/ Framework: React.js
  - Additional: Redux, API database React-bootstrap, Material UI.
  - o Project link: <a href="mailto:cyber-e0d08.web.app/">cyber-e0d08.web.app/</a>

## **EDUCATION**

Cybersoft Academy - Vietnam

03/2020 - 12/2020

Certificate in Front-end developer

Laurea University of Applied Sciences - Finland

08/2013 - 08/2017

Bachelor degree in Business Management

- English: Fluent. Finnish: Basic.

## **ACTIVITIES**

✓ Admin of Reacjs group in Discord.

Link:

https://discord.gg/waRXwWpU

## **WORKING EXPERIENCES**

March 2020 – Present: Freelance Front-end developer

> Jan 2019 – Jan 2020: Operation Manager at F-Box Palveluvarastot Оу

August 2018 – Jan 2020: Operation Manger at DL Transports

> Jan 2017- Jan 2018: Customer Service Manager at DL Transport